Notre Dame: Alumni Association
Alumni Association
- Alumni Association: Graphics, 1990s-; GALM
  - Digital Images, c2003-; GALM
    - Alumni Senate Leadership Conference, including Emil T. Hofman [10 photos, scanned from prints], 2004/04; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - A boat on the Amazon River [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - A boat on the Danube River [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - A castle in Ireland [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - A river and church in Poland [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - A city in Provence, France [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Travel - The Coliseum in Rome, Italy [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Portraits of Alumni Association staff member Chris Bellairs [2 photos], 2004/0917; GALM
    - Chuck Lennon Alumni Association PowerPoint presentation, 2004/0419; GALM
    - Notre Dame Medical Ethics Conference; photos by Katie Fredesso? [35 photos, scanned from prints], 2004; GALM
    - Notre Dame Alumni Family Hall hooked rug hanging on a wall, 2004/0731; GALM
    - The Murphy family on the Main Building steps with a banner [9 photos], 2004/0731; GALM
    - Notre Dame Alumni Association Travel Guide - A man and a woman scuba diving under water [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Notre Dame Alumni Association Travel Guide - Iguassu Falls, Brazil [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Notre Dame Alumni Association Travel Guide - The Great Sphinx of Giza and a pyramid in Egypt [stock photo], c2004; GALM
    - Alumni Association Awards Presentation luncheon, includes with Chuck Lennon, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Lou Nanni; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [21 photos], 2005/0130; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2005/0130; GALM
    - Alumni Association Awards Presentation dinner, includes with Chuck Lennon, Joan Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [22 photos], 2005/0130; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Dr. John B. "Jack" Matthews Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Joan Lennon [116 photos], 2005/1111; GALM
    - Alumni Association Corby Hall Awards Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Mike Brown, Rev. Paul Doyle [133 photos], 2005/1126; GALM
    - Alumni Association Thomas Dooley Award to Sr. Joan Chittister, OSB, Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Mike Brown, Joan Lennon [120 photos], 2005/1127; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - James E. Armstrong Award to Rev. Paul Doyle Dinner, including with Chuck Lennon, Emil T. Hofman; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [61 photos], 2005/0422; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Hall Spirit Awards, including with Rev. Mark Poorman; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [89 photos], 2005/0422; GALM
    - Blue-Gold Football Game Day - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Award presentations, including with Chuck Lennon, Ruth Riley; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [33 photos], 2005/0423; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - William D. Reynolds Award to Rev. Alfred F. D'Alonzo and the Rev. Louis J. Putz Award to Dr. James R. Kennedy and Elizabeth (Betsy) Finneran Kennedy, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [15 photos], 2005/0423; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - Young Alumni Awards Luncheon, including with Chuck Lennon, Mike Brown; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [25 photos], 2005/0421; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - Distinguished Alumnus Award to Ruth Riley, including with Chuck Lennon, Rev. John I. Jenkins; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [20 photos], 2005/0421; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - Club Award Presentations, including with Karen Putt; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [193 photos], 2005/0422; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Board of Directors members, including Chuck Lennon, Mike Brown; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [22 photos], 2005/0420; GALM
    - Photos used for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004-2005; GALM
      - Portrait of Father Al; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-05fr_al.psd
      - Bob, Tim, and Gene; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-BiggerBobTimGene.psd
      - Portrait of Mike Brown; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-brown-mike.tif
      - Portrait of Buckley; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-buckley0001.tif
      - Portrait of Philip Carter; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-Carter_Philip.tif
      - Cedar Grove Cemetery; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-ChapelandArchduotone.psd
      - Alumni Association Officers; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-ClOfficersP-01.psd
      - Cedar Grove Cemetery "Coming Home" logo; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-comingHomeLogo1.psd
      - Portrait of Phil Connors; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-connorsphil.tif
      - Portrait of Danny Richter; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Danny Richter1.psd
      - Notre Dame professor emeritus Emil T. Hofman with children in South America?; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-emildutone.psd
      - Portrait of Rev. Paul Doyle; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Fr-Doyle.psd
      - A priest saying Mass at the Grotto; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-grotto.psd
      - Three men and a truck (Alumni Club volunteer service event?); for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-guysandtruck.psd
      - Portrait of Homer couple; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Homer05.psd
      - Portrait of John Coyle; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-johnCoyle.psd
      - Portrait of Keegan; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-keegan.tif
      - Portrait of Jerry Kruczek; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-kruczekjerry.tif
      - Portrait of Kennedy couple; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Kennedy05.psd
      - Portrait of Kreigshauser; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-kriegshauser.tif
      - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference? - Three women reading materials in an auditorium; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-ladiesreading.psd
      - Portrait of an unidentified woman; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-lady.psd
      - Alumni Association Notre Dame desk lamp; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Lamp.psd
      - Portrait of Mike; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-mike.psd
      - Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy talking with Rev. John I. Jenkins; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-monk_jenkins.psd
      - A man talking with a young man (a Marine?), who is on crutches; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-NDSA_Marines_2.psd
      - A group of children playing with a pinata; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-pinata.psd
      - Portrait of Prinster; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-prinster.tif
      - A woman surrounded by children; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-SCN-I.psd
      - Portrait of Rev. Will Seetch; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2004; GALM-2005-SeetchWill.psd
      - Portrait of Shannon Gayk; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-shannon-gayk.psd
      - Back design of The Shirt; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, GALM-2005-shirt2005backduo.psd
      - Front design of The Shirt; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, GALM-2005-shirt2005frontduo.psd
      - A group of Notre Dame Alumni in Sydney, Australia; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Sydney.pdf
      - Portrait of Tom Sullivan; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, c2005; GALM-2005-Tom Sullivan05.psd
      - A male student studying in a dorm room, c1930s; for a 2005 Alumni Association newsletter, GALM-2005-youngoldguy.psd
    - Alumni Association Reunion, including at banquets, Mass, golf, beer tents, registration, tours, and with Chuck Lennon, Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy, Lou Nanni, Rev. James Riehle [205 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award to Michael (Mike) P. McCoy Reception, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [34 photos], 2005/1021; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Brigham Young University (BYU) - Alumni Association Harvey G. Foster Award Presentation to Michael (Mike) P. McCoy, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [14 photos], 2005/1022; GALM
    - An Alumni Association tourist group in South America on an Amazon voyage, including with Emil T. Hofman; photos by G. Greer [16 photos], 2005/05; GALM
    - Alumni Association Asian Pacific Alumni Awards Dinner, including with Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy, Lou Nanni, Karen Putt; photos by Michael (Mike) Bennett (MLB) [214 photos], 2005/0603; GALM
    - Alumni Association Florida Fling at Jupiter Beach Resort, including with Chuck Lennon [60 photos; photos may have been scanned from a negative, not born-digital], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Family Volunteer Camp (FVC); photos by Jackie [64 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Rev. John I. Jenkins Inauguration as University President, with the focus on Notre Dame Alumni, including with Chuck Lennon, Emil T. Hofman, Bishop John D'Arcy, Rev. Peter Rocca [49 photos], 2005/0923; GALM
    - Rev. Edward "Monk" Malloy signing books in the Alumni Association Eck Visitors Center [4 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Students studying in the Eck Visitors Center auditorium while they wait for their turn in the Alumni Association Notre Dame vs. Purdue football game ticket sales [3 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Sunlight hitting the top of a tree on campus [3 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Dedication of the Rev. Edmund P. Joyce and Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh Statue outside of Hesburgh Library, including with Rev. John I. Jenkins, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, John Affleck-Graves; photos by Heather Gollatz Dukeman [27 photos, scanned from negatives], 2005/1022; GALM
    - New Alumni Board Member Candidates, individual portraits of Philip Carter, Dan Brosmer, Eileen Doran, Ernie Buckley, George Harvey, Jerry Kruczek, Jim Kane, Keegan, K.J. Lethbridge, Kriegshauser, Mark Brooke, Mike Brown, Phil Connors, Prinster, Rich Bollini, 2005; GALM
    - New Alumni Board Member Candidates - HighMAT files, 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association staff members; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2005/1020; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors Group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2005/1020; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors - Individual portraits including Jerry Kruczek, Ernie Buckley, Kriegshauer, Mike Brown, Phil Connors, Philip Carter, Keegan, Prinster; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [36 photos], 2005/1020; GALM
    - Alumni Association Past Presidents Group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2005/1021; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board Presidents including Jean Collier [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Danielle and John at an Alumni Association meeting [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Executive Committee [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association - Gene, Margo, and Carol Mullaney [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Alumni Board members who were lunch guess at Holy Cross House [wpd document converted to docx; both in file], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association - Jean Collier and Cindy [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association - Kevin and Chuck Lennon [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association group project with a potato [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House [12 photos total, scanned from prints], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Rev. Charlie Kohlerman, CSC, religious superior at Holy Cross House, expresses his appreciation on behalf of the priests, and hands the microphone over to Alumni Board President Jean Collier [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.01
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Joanne Clayback with Rev. George Kahle, CSC, and Rev. Bob Hoffman, CSC [photos scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.02 and .04
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Brother Paul Loos, CSC, welcomes Steve Fattor '83 of Albuquerque [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.05
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Bob Goyette joins Rev. Jim Tobin, CSC, at his table [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.06
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Rev. Bill Hickens, CSC, talks with Stacy Roscoe [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.07
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Rev. Adrian Ste. Marie, CSC (foreground), invites Arnie Testa to dine at his table, while Rev. Dan Coughlin welcomes John Greer [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.08
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Jean Collier introduces herself to Rev. Bill Botzum, CSC, and Rev. Michael Scully, CSC [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.09
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Michelle Strathman greets Rev. Bill Hickens, CSC. In the background are Rev. Jim Tobin, CSC; Rev. Bill O'Connor, CSC; Rev. Michael Scully, CSC; and Rev. Paul Rankin, CSC [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.10
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Rev. Charlie Kohlerman, CSC, Chuck Lennon, Frank McGehee, Stacy Roscoe '71, Ventura CA; and Carol Mullaney [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.11
    - Alumni Association Lunch at Holy Cross House - Rev. Bob Pelton, CSC, and Joanne Clayback, Buffalo NY [photo scanned from a print], 2005; GALM-2005-Untitled.12
    - Alumni Association meeting workshop, including with Jean Collier [5 photos], 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Young Alumni Directors, 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Native American Board Member portraits [9 photos, scanned from prints], 2005; GALM
    - Rev. John I. Jenkin's signature, 2005; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Captain Jack J. Samar Jr. Reception, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [47 photos], 2006/1117; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Army - Alumni Association flag-raising ceremony with Rev. William Corby Award winner Captain Jack J. Samar Jr., including with the Army ROTC Color Guard, Marching Band, Irish Guard, Band Director Larry Dwyer; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [13 photos], 2006/1118; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Army - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award presentation to Captain Jack J. Samar Jr., including with Chuck Lennon, John Affleck-Graves, Chris Zorich, Army ROTC Color Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [14 photos], 2006/1118; GALM
    - Alumni Association Irish Madonna Statue; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2007/0412; GALM
    - Alumni Association Irish Madonna Statue plaque honoring Frank O'Brien III; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0412; GALM
    - Blue-Gold Football Game Day - Alumni Association William D. Reynolds Award to Michael J. Kennelly Presentation, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Joe Raymond [22 photos], 2007/0421; GALM
    - Alumni Association William D. Reynolds Award to Michael J. Kennelly Reception, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Joe Raymond [86 photos], 2007/0421; GALM
    - Portrait of Alumni Association Board of Directors member Cathy Connors; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2007/0706; GALM
    - Alumni Association Black Alumni Board of Directors group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Black Alumni Board of Directors members; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [21 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Alumni Association Asian-Pacific Alumni Board of Directors group, including Michael Wong; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Asian-Pacific Alumni Board of Directors members; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [6 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Alumni Association Hispanic Alumni Board of Directors group; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Hispanic Alumni Board of Directors members; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [12 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Alumni Association Native American Alumni Board of Directors group, including Michael Wong; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [3 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Native American Alumni Board of Directors members; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [18 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Portrait of Alumni Association staff member Marc Burdell; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [4 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Portrait of Alumni Association staff member Meeghan Mousaw; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Portrait of Alumni Association staff member Karen Putt; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [3 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Portrait of an unidentified Alumni Association staff member; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [2 photos], 2007/0914; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Brigadier General Philip Volpe Reception, including with Chuck Lennon; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [55 photos], 2007/1102; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Navy - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Brigadier General Philip Volpe Presentation, including with Chuck Lennon, Naval ROTC Color Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman? [20 photos], 2007/1103; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. Navy - Alumni Association Flag-raising ceremony with Rev. William Corby Award recipient Brigadier General Philip Volpe, including with Chuck Lennon, Naval ROTC Color Guard, Irish Guard, Marching Band, Band Director Larry Dwyer; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [33 photos], 2007/1103; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion Opening Reception, including with Karen Putt; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [30 photos], 2007/0531; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion Flag Retreat Ceremony, including with Chuck Lennon, Tim Dukeman, Naval ROTC Color Guard; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [38 photos], 2007/0531; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - John Cardinal O'Hara Award to Francis X. ("Tim") Bradley Jr. Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [41 photos], 2007/0601; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - Renewal of Marriage Vows in the Basilica of the Sacred Heart; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [11 photos], 2007/0601; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - Class of 1957 Fifty (50) Year Club Luncheon in South Dining Hall with Rev. John I. Jenkins presenting a certificate to individual alumni; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [358 photos; the file name identifies the alumnus' (one alumna) last name], 2007/0602; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion Closing Dinner in the Joyce Athletic and Convocation Center (JACC), including with Chuck Lennon, Emil T. Hofman, Provost Thomas (Tom) Burish, Naval ROTC Color Guard, Rev. John I. Jenkins, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Lou Nanni; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [81 photos], 2007/0602; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - A group of men; photo by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman, 2007/0601; GALM
    - Alumni Association Reunion - Children tie-dying tee-shirts on campus; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [14 photos], 2007/0601; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Luncheon in North Dining Hall, including Mike Brown; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [38 photos], 2007/0503; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Hall Spirit Awards Reception in North Dining Hall, including Rev. Mark Poorman, Chuck Lennon, Rev. Pete McCormick, Rev. Ralph Haag; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [71 photos], 2007/0504; GALM
    - 2001 Baseball Team 5th-year reunion poster, 2007/0913; GALM
    - 1957 Baseball Team 50th-year reunion poster, 2007/0913; GALM
    - Alumni Association Irish Madonna Statue Dedication with the O'Brien family donors, including with Chuck Lennon, Joan Lennon, Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Rev. Paul Doyle, Rev. John I. Jenkins, Rev. Mark Poorman, Lou Nanni, Kevin White, and at the Cancer Survivor and Awareness Tree outside of the Eck Visitors Center; photos by Joe Raymond [254 photos], 2007/0503; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference? Reception in North Dining Hall and award presentation at the Blue-Gold Spring Football Game, including with Chuck Lennon, Joan Lennon, Darrell "Flash" Gordon; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [122 photos], 2008/0419; GALM
    - Individual portraits of Alumni Association Board Members, including Dolly Duffy; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [40 photos], 2008/0414; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference - Alumni Club Awards Dinner, including with Chuck Lennon, Mike Brown, Darrell "Flash" Gordon; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [328 photos], 2008/0424; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference luncheon, including with Mike Brown, Meeghan Mousaw; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [45 photos], 2008/0424; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference dinner in South Dining Hall, including with Rev. Theodore M. Hesburgh, Chuck and Joan Lennon, Pat Trost; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [55 photos], 2008/0425; GALM
    - Alumni Association Senate Leadership Conference Awards luncheon, including with Mike Brown, Rev. Pete McCormick, Rev. Ralph Haag; photos by Terry Trethewey? Images Unlimited Photography [120 photos], 2008/0425; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors Weekend - Rev. John J. Cavanaugh Award to Percy Pierre Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Patricia Trost; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [71 photos], 2008/0904; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors Weekend - Harvey G. Foster Award to Bryant Young Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Patricia Trost; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [65 photos], 2008/0905; GALM
    - Alumni Association Board of Directors Weekend - Surprise award to Joan Lennon, including with Chuck Lennon, Lou Nanni; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [28 photos], 2008/0905; GALM
    - Football Game Day - Notre Dame vs. San Diego State - Flag-raising ceremony, including with the Irish Guard, Naval ROTC Color Guard, Band Director Larry Dwyer; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [32 photos], 2008/0906; GALM
    - Alumni Association Rev. William Corby Award to Lieutenant General Henry A. "Trey" Obering III Reception, including with Chuck Lennon, Joan Lennon, Tim Dukeman, Paige Snyder, Dolly Duffy; photos by Heather Gollatz-Dukeman [80 photos], 2008/1003; GALM